daewoo.com.pk 2017-12-20

# Privacy | Daewoo Pakistan Express Bus Service

## Daewoo Express Privacy Policy

Thank you for using the Daewoo Express Website & Mobile Application. We respect your privacy and want to protect your personal information. To learn more, please read this Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy explains how we collect, use and (under certain conditions) disclose your personal information. This Privacy Policy also explains the steps we have taken to secure your personal information.

## Data that we collect

We may collect various pieces of information if you seek to book a bus or buy a ticket using our mobile app or our website. We collect, store and process your data for processing your purchase on the App and any possible later claims, and to provide you with our services. We may collect personal information including, but not limited to, your title, name, gender, email address, telephone number, mobile number, payment details, payment card details or mobile wallet account details.

We will use the information you provide to enable us to process your orders and to provide you with the services and information offered through our website/mobile app and which you request. Further, we will use the information you provide to administer your account with us; verify and carry out financial transactions in relation to payments you make online; audit the downloading of data from our website/mobile app; improve the layout and/or content of the pages of our website/mobile app and customize them for users; identify visitors on our website/mobile app; carry out research on our users' demographics; send you information we think you may find useful or which you have requested from us, including information about our services, provided you have indicated that you have not objected to being contacted for these purposes. 

Payments that are made through the website/mobile app will be processed by our relevant agent. However, we do not store any credit card or bank detail information on our server. This information is stored with the bank on their secure servers and we are only given an identifier. 

You undertake to treat the personal access data confidentially and not make it available to unauthorized third parties. We cannot assume any liability for misuse of passwords unless this misuse is our fault.

If you choose to provide us with personal information, you consent to the transfer and storage of that information on our servers.

## Other usage of your personal information

We may use your personal information for opinion and market research. Your details are anonymous and will only be used for statistical purposes. Any answers to surveys or opinion polls we may ask you to complete will not be forwarded on to third parties. Disclosing your email address is only necessary if you would like to take part in competitions. We save the answers to our surveys separately from your email address.

We may also send you other information about us, the website/mobile app, our other websites, our products, promotions, anything relating to other companies in our group or our business partners. 

## Third parties and links

We may pass your details to other companies in our group. We may also pass your details to our agents and subcontractors to help us with any of our uses of your data set out in our Privacy Policy. We may exchange information with third parties for the purposes of fraud protection and credit risk reduction.

Other than as set out in this Privacy Policy, we shall NOT sell or disclose your personal data to third parties without obtaining your prior consent unless this is necessary for the purposes set out in this Privacy Policy or unless we are required to do so by law.

## Security

We have in place appropriate technical and security measures to prevent unauthorized or unlawful access to or accidental loss of or destruction or damage to your information. When we collect data through the website/mobile app, we collect your personal details on a secure server. We use firewalls on our servers. Our security procedures mean that we may occasionally request proof of identity before we disclose personal information to you. You are responsible for protecting against unauthorized access to your password and to your computer.

## Your rights

If you are concerned about your data you have the right to request access to the personal data which we may hold or process about you. You have the right to require us to correct any inaccuracies in your data free of charge. At any stage you also have the right to ask us to stop using your personal data for direct marketing purposes.
